<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Lucky Red Lantern</title>
 <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="/"/>
 <updated>2022-10-25T18:37:19+00:00</updated>
 <id></id>
 <author>
   <name>Olivier Milla</name>
   <email>olivier.milla@hey.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Fixing NFT floor prices with blind auctions.</title>
   <link href="/2021/09/16/fixing-nft-floors-with-blind-auctions"/>
   <updated>2021-09-16T17:42:19+00:00</updated>
   <id>/2021/09/16/Fixing-NFT-floors-with-blind-auctions</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is a design proposal to solve the problem of “Index Reliability” presented by the VC firm Paradigm &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paradigm.xyz/2021/08/floor-perps/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, the problem is that for any financial derivative contract to exist, it needs an underlying value/price to track. What is commonly done on NFT marketplaces such as OpenSea is to define the “floor price” as the lowest offered price on any item of an NFT collection and use that as the underlying price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike BTC, ETH or any other token, the liquidity of an NFT collection is limited by the edition size and the offered liquidity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a side effect, NFT prices are updated much less often and can even present gaps, making it hard to create derivatives with reasonable initial/maintenance margins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, “floor prices” only take the supply into account without bothering whether there is any real demand at these levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see if we can do better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/nft-auction.gif&quot; alt=&quot;NFT auction&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-we-seek&quot;&gt;What we seek&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to be able to produce an NFT series Price Index.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-we-seek&quot;&gt;Why we seek&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We want to do that to give people access to synthetic exposure, either long or short to NFT series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are our options?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;option-1--current-opensea-floor-price&quot;&gt;Option 1 — Current OpenSea Floor Price&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s using a definition of a floor price equal to the lowest SELL order on the entire NFT series. There are several problems with this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It relies on a single item in the series which makes the floor volatile. if you are the owner of the NFT, you have direct access to the index. Update your price up and the index moves up. Same on the way down.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The fact that this item is ‘trailing’ the others in the series could be for some external factors which are not representative of the series.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cool thing though is that it’s simple. It says that if you want to know how much you have to pay to get one (possibly the worst of the series), here is the price you have to pay right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;option-2--the-realized-price&quot;&gt;Option 2 — The Realized Price&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use the realized price:&lt;/p&gt;

\[IndexPrice=\sum_{i=1}^{N}LastPrice_i\]

&lt;p&gt;This represents the value committed in the series, either on the primary or secondary market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-good-parts&quot;&gt;The good parts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have a price as soon as 1 item in the series is sold on the primary market.
You have no dependency to liquidity. Days can go by without any trade and you’ll be good.
The Index price evolution is smoothed by the series’ size.
No faking the order book game. The only way to move the index is to trade an NFT of the series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-bad-parts&quot;&gt;The bad parts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On either side of the market, you can take a leveraged position on a derivative tracking the Index Price and manipulate it at profit. That is if the cost of buying the j lowest-priced items in the series is less than the gain you will have on your leveraged position. You can then exit your leveraged position and sell back the j items at a price totaling less than the gain you made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;variations&quot;&gt;Variations&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can have the price expressed in USD base currency with either the ETH/USD current quote or quote at the time of the ith transaction.
The good thing here is that if the NFT series are sold in both DAI or ETH, it still works.
Note that using the current ETH/USD quote implies an update rate of the index price at a faster rate to avoid arbitrage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;option-3--blind-auctions&quot;&gt;Option 3 — Blind auctions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It goes like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holders of an item in the NFT series place a minimum price at which they are ready to part with their item. That is the supply S.
People who wish to acquire an item of the series place a maximum price at which they are ok for a purchase. That is the demand D.
Nobody knows what any other actor is doing. That is: The people placing an order on either side don’t know if there are other participants on their side or the other side and don’t know the prices or items that participate in the auction.
Supply and demand are matched and cleared where&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;\(IndexPrice=ClearingPrice=\frac{\sum_{i=1}^{j}D_i}{j}\) if \(max(D_i)\geq min(S_i)\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;\(IndexPrice=max(D_i)\) if \(max(D_i)\lt min(S_i)\)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;\($IndexPrice=min(S_i)\) if there is at least 1 offer (supply side).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In picture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/auction-result.png&quot; alt=&quot;NFT auction&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;notes&quot;&gt;Notes&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If a Clearing Price is found an actual transfer of j NFT for cash occurs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Otherwise you get no transfer but you still get an Index Price of the maximum price somebody is willing to pay to get any NFT from the series or if no demand, the minimum of the supply, which should be equal to Option1.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is key, that each participant’s preference is respected but the floor price is actually a unique clearing price for all the transfers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The fact that the auction is hidden forces all the participants to price NFTs for the personal economic value they see. It means that the floor price here is actually much more informed than if participants had access to the other participants orders.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There’s a hedge case where nobody shows up at the auction. While I believe that people will create such a market only for items of interest (aka there is a demand), it’s possible and we could use a fallback method (Option1) or last auction’s Index Price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-good-things-are&quot;&gt;The good things are:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is hard to rig because as soon as you place an order, it may get filled.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;But placing an order does not allow you to easily modify the Index Price because&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;if your price is set to the Index Price, it means it is the highest demand, hence the riskier order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;the demand side is open and hence anyone can actually have the upper hand either through clearing or out bidding you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;in the end, the only thing you can know for sure when placing such an order is that you can trade at the floor or not trade at all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OK, I see BID and ASK orders here, so why not just go for an order book?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Glad you ask. Because the floor price here is in fact &lt;strong&gt;a mutualized floor price&lt;/strong&gt; of the series. It means it can only exist &lt;strong&gt;when orders are placed at the same time to be cleared together&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you were to use an order book, the likelihood that you could clear more than 1 order at the same time would be very low and your Index Price will look like Option1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what auctions for fixing prices are for.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Auctions with variable supply in crypto NFT markets.</title>
   <link href="/2021/09/07/auctions-with-variable-supply-in-nft-markets"/>
   <updated>2021-09-07T06:42:19+00:00</updated>
   <id>/2021/09/07/auctions-with-variable-supply-in-nft-markets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview&quot;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This paper introduces an auction design for NFT series that allows for a better equilibrium between demand and supply.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It does so by creating an auction where participants (both creators and bidders) state their preferences in terms of both PRICE and EDITION SIZE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The design allows the creators to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maximize their revenues.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach their maximum audience within price and edition size boundaries that they control.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Provide a fair distribution, giving all successful bidders the same NFT price (aka floor).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preserve their brands, as failed NFT auctions can destroy the trust your customers place when they enter an auction for one of your series. If they do that regularly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also allows bidders to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enter auctions more safely by allowing them to place both price and edition size limits outside of which they wish not to participate. This allows them to trade within their budget but also to target an edition size minimum (below which they consider the NFT auction a failure) and maximum (after which they consider the NFTs are not scarce enough for them).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enter auctions more efficiently as the design lessens the gas race that can occur on fixed-size auctions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both creators and bidders benefit from the fact that the equilibrium found with that design is less volatile post-auction as it finds an equilibrium both in terms of price AND market size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is particularly important for NFTs that have utilities/constraints/interactions/upsells later on during their lifetime, allowing for a secondary market to open in a more price-stable way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;What is the best way to distribute NFTs without gas wars?&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; defiprime (@defiprime) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/defiprime/status/1434644596579913729?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;September 5, 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-problem&quot;&gt;The Problem&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;from-the-point-of-view-of-the-creator&quot;&gt;From the point of view of the creator&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each creator has its preference regarding the NFT size they see fit:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some creators want to express “I created the new Mona Lisa, there shall be 3 NFTs and no more”.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some creators want to create an edition targeting a community/market size. These opportunities have an equilibrium at which they function. Too few is a failure and too many is a failure.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some creators want to optimize for REACH. This is equivalent to optimizing for a maximum number of users.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Some creators also simply have technical constraints. For instance, generative arts algorithms could generate only max N variations. Or if the NFT is used to grant access to a Discord channel, they wish that channel to be of a manageable size.
Creators also obviously seek to maximize their revenues.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;from-the-point-of-view-of-the-bidders&quot;&gt;From the point of view of the bidders&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bidders also have preferences for entering an auction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether it is an art they are buying, access to a market or a key to a community, they each have&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a budget&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a desire to buy the NFT at the same price as everyone else during the auction.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a desire to pay the smallest price possible.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;supply boundaries that they prefer:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Some art collectors only deal with very scarce items, similarly to art collectors and don’t want to enter a crowded market.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Some others have boundaries, for instance for in-game NFTs where they know the mechanics and they are ok to purchase something if there are enough of it, and not too many.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Some others want to buy their NFTs whatever the edition size. They just like the stuff and have no price and/or edition size boundaries&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-solution&quot;&gt;The solution&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution is to design an auction where&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-creator-specifies&quot;&gt;the creator specifies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a minimum and maximum edition size. The minimum size is your kickstarter target. You may want to cancel the entire thing (and try again later with more marketing) if not enough NFTs are minted for the game to function otherwise the few people who showed up could feel scammed. The maximum edition is the hard limit of the mint.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a minimum revenue that applies to the whole edition below which they are ready to cancel the whole thing and refund the participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-bidders-specify&quot;&gt;the bidders specify&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a minimum and a maximum NFT price. Outside this zone, they do not wish to participate.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a minimum and maximum edition size. If the edition size is outside these boundaries, they do not wish to participate either.
    &lt;h2 id=&quot;solving-multiple-possible-equilibrium-solutions&quot;&gt;Solving multiple possible equilibrium solutions&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Multiple solutions may provide the same revenue to the creator. They can then either decide on the solution they prefer either by&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;time of arrival. (current gas war)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;edition size (creators choose to select either the smallest edition size or the biggest)
random choice&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Or a combination of them (first the edition size, if there are still multiple solutions, the time of arrival or a random solution).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, current gas war auctions are a special case of this auction design where they set&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No minimum revenue at the edition level.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Hard minimum and maximum edition size, set to the same value.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Give the users no choice but to pay for the gas war by not giving them edition size boundaries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;extensions&quot;&gt;Extensions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of constraints can be added or removed. For instance, if your NFTs have in-game mechanisms or characteristics that require that some NFTs are present from day one, you can add constraints that allow for an auction to succeed only if some quantities are met or you can prioritize certain NFTs over others for the game to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;technicalities&quot;&gt;Technicalities&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An algorithm may take a lo(ooooo)ong time to solve such an auction and it probably can’t run fully on chain (I’m no expert here, feel free to comment). It would probably take an on-chain with an off-chain ping-pong to work.
Last but not least, it works for fungible tokens too, helping projects find the right price and supply for an ICO/ECO.
Reach out on Twitter if you’re interested in discussing the topic in public or private, DMs are open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some Links on the subject&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.simondlr.com/posts/maximising-blockchain-collectible-economies&quot;&gt;Maximising Blockchain Collectible Economies — (simondlr.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.simondlr.com/posts/exploring-nft-economies&quot;&gt;Exploring NFT Economies: Creators, Collectors, &amp;amp; Collection Sizes. — (simondlr.com)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;edit&quot;&gt;Edit&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is also possible to factor in the bidders’ preference in terms of quantity of items acquired: “I want to acquire at least X items and at most Y” but as well as the percentage of ownership: “I want to acquire at least W% and at most Z% of the items”.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Always on sales and NFTs.</title>
   <link href="/2021/08/21/always-on-sales-and-nft"/>
   <updated>2021-08-21T13:42:19+00:00</updated>
   <id>/2021/08/21/always-on-sales-and-nft</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I recently came across a Twitter thread proposing a financial engineering solution applying an &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@simondlr/what-is-harberger-tax-where-does-the-blockchain-fit-in-1329046922c6&quot;&gt;Harberger Tax to NFTs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Harbenger tax -&amp;gt; re-thinking markets from the ground up. 2 core concepts:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Users value their own assets and pay tax continuously on that value &lt;br /&gt;2) At any point in time, anyone else can buy the asset from you at that price, forcing a sale &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/cp5psshTEj&quot;&gt;https://t.co/cp5psshTEj&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Amber Group (@ambergroup_io) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ambergroup_io/status/1428934731186327560?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;August 21, 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harberger Tax is designed to address the problem that ownership is a monopoly. Simply put, once you are the owner of something, no one can force you to part from it. It is only you who can decide to put your asset on the market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Harberger’s idea is to&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Force you to always publish a price at which you would be willing to sell.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pay a tax, say every year, as a percentage of the price you published.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason this is great is that it forces you to fairly price your economic opportunity, pay the tax that goes with it and allow anyone to buy that ownership for a greater economic opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more about it over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.radicalxchange.org/&quot;&gt;RadicalXChange&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our case, the core issue is that some NFTs are being snatched by buyers at auctions and leave a lot of person with no access to it. They also can leave sellers with a less valuable outcome. A problem recently addressed by Vitalik Buterin who is proposing &lt;a href=&quot;https://vitalik.ca/general/2021/08/22/prices.html&quot;&gt;a design on how to have more equalitarian access to NFTs/fixed supply tokens sold through auctions/ICOs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An experiment has already been done to use something like Harberger Tax by Simon de la Rouviere with &lt;a href=&quot;https://thisartworkisalwaysonsale.com/&quot;&gt;This Artwork Is Always On Sale&lt;/a&gt;. His idea is that the tax rate is patronage to the artist. That is the artist gets ‘dividends’ from his work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can read more about it &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.simondlr.com/posts/this-artwork-is-always-on-sale-v2&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this goes in the direction of better market forces but there are other points of view. For instance:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;6/ NFTs are built different.   &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are 18 hoodie nerd glasses punks or 20 squiggles perfect spectrum that will eventually mostly end up in diamond hands over the next months/years as we play some musical chairs and shuffle things around&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; 6529 (@punk6529) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/punk6529/status/1423370467096895489?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;August 5, 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is said here is that punk6529 wants to be able to “defend the castle”, &lt;strong&gt;at all costs&lt;/strong&gt;. That is, by saying “no” to a transfer of ownership and hence opposes a mechanic such as always-on-sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many such people are very actively creating the myth and culture of the metaverse and arguably, without these early builders owning these NFTs NOW, we could (altogether, the commons) be left with a lesser economic opportunity than the one they are building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the opposite effect of what Harberger stands for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a way, these owners of NFT somewhat agree with the ideas of Harberger. They already agreed to give part of their ownership by &lt;a href=&quot;https://avc.com/2021/08/splitting-ownership-and-display-consumption/&quot;&gt;splitting ownership and display/consumption&lt;/a&gt; as Fred Wilson puts it. An NFT is public, anyone can see it, even ‘right-click’ it and save the underlying JPEG. But ownership is not shared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NFT in itself is off the market. It allows the owner of the NFT to signal to be part of a community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To quote &lt;a href=&quot;https://eriktorenberg.substack.com/p/signaling-on-the-internet&quot;&gt;Erik Torenberg&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Membership is the message” and the more exclusive a club is to join, or the more impressive the criteria members need in order to join, the more membership is a signal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Raising the bar is not incompatible with Harberger, but in our case, if CryptoPunks were always-on-sale, speculation would possibly dilute or eviscerate some of the community behind it. Leaving it off the market protects the community from being invaded by &lt;a href=&quot;https://meaningness.com/geeks-mops-sociopaths&quot;&gt;MOPs and sociopaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will find a way. And the community will be back to trading opinions. Intangibles, can’t be traded. And that’s what punk6529 wishes for:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;jekyll-twitter-plugin&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;What they want is being able to &amp;quot;defend the castle&amp;quot;, at all cost. That is, by saying &amp;quot;no&amp;quot; to a transfer of ownership. The key point is that without these people owning these NFTs NOW, we could (altogether) be left with a lesser economic opportunity than the one they are building.&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Picaroon Inc. (@picarooninc) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/picarooninc/status/1429537396769632258?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;August 22, 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
